Darling, Darling?
Sailing
on the
cobalt blue!
The clouds float above the sea!
Hanging out
just me and you!
Our time is now and soon you'll see!
Smile with all your heart as you go
past the problems that await you!
Keep your hopes alive!
Never look down upon yourself!
Just cast a magic spell!
You will get through!
Crazy, crazy rainbow!
Star, twinkle, twinkle rainbow star!
Fast beats premonition!
Just like the colors from
all the rainbow beams!
Crazy, crazy rainbow!
Star, come with me and we'll go far!
We're just fallen angels!
Shooting arrows into our hopeful dreams!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
I'm a crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle rainbow star!
Within the cobalt blue!
Seven colors will come to our surprise!
Crazy, crazy rainbow star!
Twinkle, twinkle rainbow star!
Abandon all your worries!
Your troubles show through
the mirror of your eyes!
Let me comfort you, my love!
I'll hold your time within my glove!
We sure are fallen angels!
Just singing our hearts
all out from up above!
Dying, dying!
Crazy, crazy hippo star!
I'm a crazy hippo star!
Anyway, Luffy, since you're my grandson,
I won't capture you and turn
you over to the government.
It's fine.
If I tell them that, I'm sure
everyone will understand.
Can't put work before family, right?
That's not an excuse, sir.
Let's just say they got away.
I mostly just came here as
a favor to Kobe and Helmepo.
You boys take your time and
chat it up all you like.
I'm heading back to my ship for now.
All right, so long!
Is that all you're gonna say?
At least pretend like you care I'm your
grandpa and you haven't seen me in ages.
I'm happy you're leaving all
you've done is yell and hit me.
I still want my grandson to love me
you idiot I'm not as heartless as you.
I see stubbornness runs in
the family and maturity too.
That old man blew in and
flew out like a storm.
I admit the part about dragons
certainly surprised me.
And here I thought my
family history was odd.
Where's Luffy?
He's out front with
Kobe and that other guy.
You don't want to see him too?
You're old friends, right?
Well, this does bring back memories.
But Luffy's the one who saved Kobe.
Not me. Huh.
I wonder where Nami ran off to.
She said something about
getting info from the Navy.
But I guess she changed her mind.
She said she went to the
pool with Kokoro and the...
The pool?
Galley-La has a company pool in the
back for all of its employees to use.
Does that mean Nami's in a swimsuit?
I better bring her a drink!
So you guys went over that mountain
to get to the Grand Line, too?
That mountain?
Oh, you mean reverse mountain.
No, we went a different way.
Well, it's top secret, but there is
another way for the Navy, at least.
That is to say, they have ships at headquarters
that can sail through the Calm Belt.
What?
How the heck is anyone supposed
to get through when the whole
ocean there is packed with sea
kings as big as battleships?
That place gave us a lot
of trouble, you know.
The catch is,
the hulls of the navy ships
that sail through there
have a bunch of sea prism
stones strapped to them.
What does that do?
Uh, I'll try to explain it.
The sea prism stones put off the
same energy as the sea itself,
so when the fish see the
bottoms of the ship...
The same energy as the sea.
So that's it.
That way, even if they go straight
through a nest of sea kings,
the monsters won't attack because
they won't notice anything.
So,
even if they didn't take the
entrance at Reverse Mountain,
they can still slip into the
Grand Lime without any trouble.
Interesting.
Those Navy scientists are
really something else.
Keep talking, guys.
This is good.
Hey, pirate lady, are you going
to swim or not? Huh? Huh? Hello?
Could you can it for just a second?
A chance like this
doesn't come very often.
I thought you were cool, Pipe Man.
You're nothing for a big, stupid joke.
I'm trying to wiretap here.
Is that something you
want to yell out loud?
The Navy has the greatest inventor
in the world working for them.
His name is Dr. Vegapunk.
He's the one who came up with this plan.
And that's only the tip
of the iceberg for him.
You know that Devil Fruits made Straw Hat?
He's the one who identified its power.
He also figured out how they'd
transfer their abilities.
He even developed a way to feed
Devil Fruits to inanimate objects.
That was his biggest project last year.
Dr. Vegapunk.
I don't get it, but
that sounds pretty cool.
The world is full of amazing people.
You know, if I had never met you,
I'd probably still be living
in a narrow little world.
I wouldn't know a thing
about the Grand Line.
It seems like forever ago, when you
burst out of that barrel on the ship.
But who knows how long I would have been
swabbing decks for Alvida
if you didn't show up.
I forgot!
You were on our ship, weren't you?
Man, that's really funny,
and the reason you were there in
the first place is even funnier!
I haven't heard this one.
You're gonna tell me the story, too.
But still I'm glad the
vice admiral is looking
out for us that's why
we have to try our best.
No matter what we do
so we can pay him back
someday yeah I'd like to
pay him back all right?
Yeah, Grillo's punches to the head.
I've been left with that one.
Maybe not today, but give it some time.
What?
You guys are going back already?
Stick around for dinner, at least.
At the end of the day,
we're still enemies.
We can't be too friendly with each other.
By the way,
I was wondering if you've
ever heard the name
they use for the second
half of the Grand Line.
At the far reaches of the ocean is a place
that few pirates or
marines have ever seen.
They call it the New World.
The New World.
There's a new era coming
and the people who
can guide it are gathering on those seas.
They say the one who can master those
waters will become King of the Pirates.
And I believe that one of these days,
you and I will meet on those waters.
And when that time comes, I'll be even
stronger, strong enough to capture you.
Because I promised myself
that I'll keep trying...
Till...
Till I become a marine admiral!
No!
I'm sorry!
I got carried away!
This is so embarrassing!
I just want to dig a hole
and bury my head in it!
That was really arrogant of me!
I got worked up after seeing
you again and I just...
Kobe...
You said you're gonna fight me, right?
Then you will become that strong!
You'll have to!
Yeah, but a marine admiral, next time I
see you, we're going to be stronger too.
A whole lot stronger.
I don't get it.
I just blurted out some ridiculous dream.
dream.
Something I don't even
have a right to follow.
But he didn't laugh.
He believed
in me.
Look at that.
Turns out you're still
a crybaby after all.
Huh, Kobe?
I'm truly grateful that I was
able to see you again today.
Keeping up with them is going to be a real
challenge I can't kid myself about this.
Just you wait we're gonna
get tougher and tougher
you'll see next time when we
all meet in the new world.
Farewell hey wait you two
better prepare yourselves
because kobe and I are
gonna blow you away.
You hear me kobe slow
down I can't slow down
I'm gonna run all the
way to the new world.
What you've lost your mind
well luffy you've done it again
you found another powerful
rival for our crew to fight.
If kobe says he can do
it then I believe him.
Here you go!
Nami sweet!
The water water meat is all ready! Yay!
Granny, that was awesome!
That meat sure smells nice. I know.
Now say ah.
Uh...
This is yummy!
Yummy!
Water, water, meat barbecue!
Silver King, where'd you come from?
Eat all you want.
I don't care anymore.
What the hell are you crying for?
I'm not crying.
I just got smoke in my eyes, that's all.
So how is it, Robin?
Nice and juicy, huh?
Yes, it's heavenly.
Look, it's them!
Hey, Straw Hat, are you finally awake?
Oh, it's your Franky family.
Get over here and eat!
Barbecue time, boys!
We've got too many cars
in two little weeks.
I want to get some more!
It's Sodom and Gomorrah!
Hey, save some for me! Me too!
Guys, over here! Hey! Hey!
Feeling better now?
No, you're out here too!
Who said you could use
the company pool anyway?
Put on some clothes! Geez!
You've never seen a swimsuit before?
Wow, something smells
delicious. Don't look, sir!
This perverted harlot is gonna corrupt
your eyes with her filthy body!
Really now?
We can't take a break once
we start building this ship!
That's why we're gonna get all
our partying done right now!
I know you got a seat set aside for me.
Because Big Bro's the
star of the show. Wow!
We're glad you could make it, bro!
All right, let's rock!
How would you like to hear
Sniper King's number one hit?
Yeah!
Party time!
Stay where you are and listen, Niko-Rom.
Aokiji?
Why didn't you try to
escape like you usually do?
If you'd acted on your own, you
could have gotten away from CP9.
Even you should know that
this time was different.
I couldn't just abandon my crew.
I couldn't leave them to die.
You might not know this,
but your friend Jaguar D.
saw that I was forced to kill
Inohara, who was my friend too.
Although I carried out my
duty as a Marine that day,
I also honored his wishes by
sparing you and helping you escape.
After that I still felt
responsible for your
life but when 20 years
had passed and you still
hadn't found a home I
began to fear Sol had made
a mistake in the end even
I had decided you were
too dangerous to live I
was certain that Annie's
lobby would end the
story of Ohara once and
for all Of course I never
anticipated that Straw
Hat's little gang would
have defeated all of CP9
so have you finally found the place
where you belong in the end I don't
know if Saul was right I don't know
if what I've done is right or not
either so now I need you to show me
the answer to that question I intend
to then live your life with courage
and prove that Ohara is still alive
How cagey!
Hey, Robin!
Check this out!
Hurry, Robin, look!
Robin!
Oh, that's me, Kenyui!
Oh, my God!
Seriously, could you guys grow up already?
Whatever, you were stepping
your face a second ago, too!
I hope these are the friends
you've been searching for.
You were right, Saul.
Hey, Robin!
Here, check it out!
Maybe I should try that myself.
Yeah, Robin! Do it! Do it!
You're a bad influence, Luffy.
Don't encourage her.
You just cooked the meat.
Don't tell us how to eat it.
Elder Stars, this is terrible.
It's an emergency.
Well, speak up.
In the New World, one of the four
emperors has broken through our lines.
Whitebeard, Edward Newgate has
crossed paths with the second emperor,
Red-Haired Shanks,
and they seem to be preparing for
some sort of meeting as we speak.
What?
Hey, Pops!
Red-Haired's ship is here!
He wants to have a meeting!
Fine, then. Let him.
That little punk better have some booze
for me, if he knows what's good for him.
He really broke through the entire fleet?
Yeah, that's what they say.
Red hair and white beard, huh?
Attention!
From this point forward, we
don't know what might happen.
All men, stand by on high alert! Yes, sir!
Alright, almost there!
Raise the sails!
Captain!
Red hair is now boarding!
You ready?
Here he comes.
All of you newcomers should stand back.
You'll get knocked out.
What do you mean we'll be knocked out?
How?
Jeez, don't ask. Just go inside.
Guys, what's going on?
Why are you all falling over?
I warned you, or I tried to at least.
This is bad, Marco.
You gotta do something.
Don't panic.
They're just passing out, that's all.
Those who have a weak
will cannot withstand
the aura that surrounds
that man's every step.
The power of his Haki is impressive.
You must excuse me it's
hard to stay calm when
I'm on an enemy ship just
looking at your face.
Makes the scar that bastard
gave me ache all over
again then can I interest
you in some of this?
Fine medicinal water I
brought I came here to talk
not to fight you knock
out half my boys with Your
Haki than you offer me a
drink you got balls kid
he ain't kidding red Hair
look at this mess you made.
Ah you're Markov the first division huh.
I
Guess you want a drink too
how about you go to hell.
Hey pops you want us here?
Nah It's fine he knows better
than to pick a fight with me.
You can go.
Sake from West Blue, huh?
Never knew you were such a cheapskate.
You know, I've sailed all
the way around the world.
But I'm telling you, the first drink I
ever had still tastes the best to me.
It's a specialty for my hometown.
Give it a shot.
Yeah, not bad.
Roger, Garp, Sengoku,
there aren't many left who remember
the ocean the way it used to be.
It's been 22 years.
What do you expect?
You've made quite a leap
since then, haven't you?
I remember when you were just an
apprentice on Goldie Roger's ship.
Roger and I locked horns so
many times back in the day.
After a while, I started to
remember all the faces on his crew.
Prepare yourself, White Beard.
You're going to be Red Beard
when I'm done with you.
Because your beard is going to
be dyed red with your own blood.
Dammit, that one sounded
a lot better in my head.
Whatever happened to that red-nosed kid?
He didn't seem too bright.
Did he wind up dead or what?
Oh, Buggy, that brings me back.
When the captain was executed,
he and I parted ways at Log Town.
Never met again.
You can join my crew, Buggy. Come on!
Yeah, right!
Like I'd work under you!
I'd heard rumors that he's still a pirate.
But who knows?
The young ones may forget, but
it's still fresh in my mind.
No one talks about the old
legends anymore these days.
But if they'd seen your duel
with Hawkeye like I did,
they'd be yapping about
it till the end of time.
Still,
when you came back from
East Blue missing an arm,
You better believe the rumors were flying.
I was pretty curious myself
Now I can ask you face to face.
What enemy did you give that left arm to?
This huh, I wouldn't take you with me
anyway, you'll never make it as a pirate
I'm the greatest treasure in the world,
and then I'll be king of the pirates!
I'll show you!
Let's just say I made a bet on a new era.
If you have no regrets, then it's fine.
You know, Whitebeard, I've
fought countless battles.
And I've received countless scars as well.
But the only one that's aching
right now is this one right here.
No.
This one came from someone
who was on your crew.
Blackbeard. Teach.
And this didn't happen because
I was being careless either.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Don't deny it.
He laid low and waited for his chance.
He never became a squad leader.
He never tried to make a name for himself.
All he did was hide himself
behind your giant shadow.
And once he had enough power,
he finally made his move.
A man like that will never be satisfied.
He'll use all of his will
in order to reach the top.
And that means he'll
come after you as well.
Why don't you get to the point already?
What do you want from me?
I want you to stop Ace.
He's young, and he's more than good enough
to be the leader of the second division.
Don't get me wrong, I
know how strong he is.
Still, no matter how much you trust
him, I think this is a big mistake.
Now is simply not the time for
those two to go head-to-head.
I want you to keep your
distance from Blackbeard.
That's what I came here to ask of you.
He's laughing.
What's going on?
You snot-nosed brat.
Do you know what you're asking?
Teach murdered one of my
crewmates, one of his crewmates.
That's the one rule that
can never be broken.
Every pirate in the world knows that.
When a pirate joins my crew,
no matter how stupid they are,
they become like a son to me.
So what am I to say to the
soul of my murdered child?
You can't live in this world
without a code of conduct.
If Teach doesn't realize that on his own,
then it's my responsibility to
drill it into his thick head.
You're a hundred years too
young to boss me around, boy.
Have I made myself perfectly clear?
Then this era will spiral into chaos,
and no one will be able to stop it.
Is that supposed to frighten me, boy?
I am Whitebeard!
Dammit!
What's going on?
Maybe we should go help him.
No, wait it out.
Red hair ain't stupid enough
to start a fight here.
True, but either way, it looks
like their talk has come to an end.
Look at the sky.
The clouds know the heavens
themselves have been divided.
Hey, bro.
Iceberg's here to see you.
Right over there.
So you're really doing it.
So what?
You want to fight about it?
Wow.
No, but if you'd like, I can help you out.
Yeah, right.
You're probably just here
to mess with my head.
You've been dismantling so long,
I'm afraid your skills have dulled.
Show me your blueprints.
A reunion for Tom's workers, huh?
I hope you old pros have
room for a couple of rookies.
Yeah!
Galley Law Company is ready to go!
Let's build the Straw Hats of shit!
They're probably itching
to get off this island,
so we figured you could use a little help.
Well, I thought you
were repairing the city.
Hmm.
We were, but when we heard you were
building a new ship for the Straw Hats,
everyone packed up their stuff and
ran here as fast as they could.
You guys!
Of course I'm happy to have you!
They really touched my heart.
Mine too!
Now hop to it!
No slack at all! Ah!
Ah!
Let's show them what the Doc
won for them and I made them!
Ah!
Look it's today's newspaper they
have a big report on annie's
lobby come on don't leave us hanging
quick tell us what it says that
article is going to decide all
our fates well about that Yeah go
on there's nothing much to say
really it doesn't mention us at all
Really not a single
word nope we're saved i
thought i was gonna have
to live the rest of my
Life as a fugitive
that crazy bastard get a
load of this it's about
Straw Hat he and his crew
went Wild on Enies Lobby
his bounty should go
through the roof after
that one that's next to
Water 7 Yes i wonder
if they hijacked a sea
train to get there that
island isn't far from here
At this rate we might meet them
again if fate is kind enough to
place him in our sights We're
obligated to pull the trigger aren't we
What are we waiting for nothing let's go?
We'd better cut them off before they leave,
or before the Navy gets to them first.
Hey, hold on a second there, Teach.
We need to talk. Huh?
Three days before the Straw Hat
Pirates' new bounties shocked the world,
another history-changing of it was
about to occur not far from Water 7.
I don't get it.
The Franky family really
wrecked up the place.
Maybe your grandpa?
Like you pulled some strings and told the
government that they were
just innocent bystanders?
Nah, that's too complicated for him.
Yeah, what Luffy said!
It must be Aokiji's doing.
What a strange man.
At any rate, that's good for them.
Obviously, we're criminals.
But I would hate to see
anyone get wrapped up
in this mess and have
their whole lives ruined.
Well, good thing you feel that way,
because they had plenty to say about us.
A declaration of war on
the world government.
They even blame us for
burning down the island.
I guarantee our bounties are going to
go through the roof after this one.
Oh my gosh, does that mean
I'll finally get a bounty?
Maybe, you'll probably get something.
But mine's gonna be the big one this time.
A bright star appears, right?
What are you excited about?
Frankie's building us a ship and
we don't even have to pay for it?
Right, you were asleep
when he said that. Awesome!
I guess Frankie's not a jerk after all!
Frankie's a nice guy!
I can't wait to see how it turns out!
Good.
Now we can use the rest of our money
to buy supplies for the voyage.
Hope this one's equipped
with a weight room.
What happened to our 100 million berries?
Oh, that?
I already spent it all.
We needed to buy lots of
meat and booze for the party.
You spent all of my money?
Well, everyone was really hungry.
How could you spend so much on food?
There's hardly anything left.
Of course there isn't.
The whole town was partying with us,
and they didn't go home
until morning, remember?
Sure was fun, huh?
Since the ship's free, we'll be fine.
So no worries, right?
I just wanted nice
furniture for this ship.
Is that so wrong?
We can still check out the resale shops.
Hey, can I have some of
that money to go play with?
I'd sooner take it to the grave!
Your allowance is revoked!
Yes, ma 'am!
Huh is that Usopp?
What's that?
Really?
You want me to rejoin your crew?
Do you well?
I understand it.
Must be rough without me.
If I'm not around, things really
start to fall apart, don't they?
Okay then.
If you insist, I'll rejoin
the Straw Hat pirates.
Yeah, that does seem to be
the best way to go about it.
And that makes 23 scenarios.
Hey, Chopper?
Nice weather we're having, huh?
Let's go.
fishing.
Hey, Loopy, care to join us?
Yeah, not bad.
And there's always the
just pretend like nothing
happened and hop on
board the ship strategy.
What else?
I've decided to set out on
my own and visit Elbath.
No, please don't go.
We need you to stay.
I was just kidding.
I totally understand not wanting
to live your lives without me.
So does that mean you're
staying? Who's up?
Of course I will, dummies.
Man, I didn't know anybody could love
someone as much as you guys You guys love me!
What the hell's he doing? What an idiot.
Hey, ice for brains.
I know you're getting tired.
Why don't you take a beauty nap?
Why don't you take a nap?
I'm beat.
My body's burning up.
I'm still alive, but at this
rate, I won't be for long.
Nobody's here.
An abandoned ship.
Full of.
Broken wood and scrap iron.
Funny, huh?
I fit right in.
I gotta do something about
this useless body of mine!
I'm not going to make it.
It's finally set.
Look, the Log Pose is
pointing to the next island.
All that's left is to get our ship.
This is going to be fun.
I can't wait to see the ship myself.
But Franky said no peeking
until he's finished.
By the way, guys, you know
where that log is pointing?
Might come as a big surprise
if you're not ready.
Actually, I don't have a clue.
Come to think of it, it kind of
looks like it's pointing down a bit.
You bet it is!
Because where it's pointing
is on the bottom of the ocean.
It's called Fishman Island.
What?
We're finally going to
Fishman Island? Really?
Whoa, Sanji's acting weird!
Fishman Island, huh?
That's tricky.
Yeah, I guess so.
Is that going to be tough after
what happened in your village?
They were pirates.
Not all fishmen are going to
give us trouble like that.
See?
Everybody knows Fishman Island is awesome.
Even Zoro, and he's stupid.
Fishman Island is one of the most
famous spots on the whole Grand Line.
Beautiful mermaids leap and dive, painting
the water with their elegant tailpits.
There you can frolic with the fish
and make all your dreams come true.
Let me help, Romeo, Romeo!
Ahem.
Ha-ha.
Let me dream!
Damn it, I'm not hurting anyone!
Relax, there's Young Mermaids, too.
The thing is, even if the
place is nice to visit,
that don't mean it's easy
for people to get there.
I assume that was the case, since
it's at the bottom of the sea.
Eh, we'll figure it out on the way.
Well, on the way is a problem, too.
Take a look at today's paper
and you'll understand huh?
What is this?
14 ships have disappeared this
month alone, all in the same place.
I don't understand.
They call that patch of
water the Florian Triangle.
anyways,
you won't be making it to Fishman Island
until after you sail through there.
Every year,
over 100 ships go missing in that
area and nobody has a clue as to why.
What's spooky is that later they show up,
totally empty, without a
single crew member in sight.
Other people say they found ghost ships
with crews of dead men wandering the ocean,
lost in a haze.
You mean they're like zombies?
Scary hanging out with a bunch
of skeletons. Sounds cool.
Hanging out that's some
imagination you've got. No way!
No ghost ships for us!
Not on my watch!
We're passing straight through that place!
I mean, what really happens in there?
Who knows?
After all, nobody ever comes out of
there alive, and dead men tell no tales.
I'd be careful.
The water is dark, the fog
is thick, it swallows you up!
Many a soul has been sacrificed
to that treacherous sea,
so you better be darn ready before
you even think of setting sail.
Although some people do
call them ghost ships,
abandoned vessels are often
called treasure ships, too.
We're more likely to find a ship
filled with riches than the undead.
No, but turn down those ghost ships!
All right, leave it to me!
No, but I don't want it!
I'll stock up on plenty of
food and water before we go,
so even if we do get lost, we'll be fine.
A treasure ship, huh?
I wonder if they have swords.
Hey, pirate people!
Go ahead!
You need something?
Franky wants to talk to you guys.
He's got something big to show you.
It's been a long night, but they
finished his ship of dreams.
And boy, is it super cool!
Yeah!
You mean it's done already?
That was really fast! Of course!
That's what happens when the best shipwrights
in the world work around the clock.
You better believe it!
What are we waiting for?
Let's go! Yeah!
Strawheads!
We got bad news!
Oh, hey, you guys!
What's going on?
They look upset.
I wonder what's wrong.
To be honest, we just found
out about this ourselves.
Have you seen the wanted posters?
Wanted posters?
You've got a huge bounty
on your head, Straw Hat.
They're going to hunt you down for sure.
Actually, you've all got bounties.
The whole crew is wanted.
Took long enough. How much? Not me too.
Wanted?
No point in talking. Just look.
Wanted posters for all seven of you.
Straw Hat Luffy with a bounty
of 300 million berries.
All right! It went up!
Pirate Hunter Zoro with a
bounty of 120 million berries.
Huh.
Cat Burglar Nami with a
bounty of 16 million berries.
No!
Cotton Candy Lovin' Chopper Pet
with a bounty of 50 berries.
50?
Demon Child Robin with a
bounty of 80 million berries.
Who is that?
Black Leg Sanji, attempt
to take a photo failed.
Bounty, 77 million berries.
Hey, look, Sniper King
has one too, only 15.
Well, I know that this is
probably big news for you and all.
And I'm sure there's a lot of
pirate stuff you want to talk about.
But, uh, hold on a sec, okay?
I came here because I got
a favor to ask of you guys.
Take a look at this.
It's Franky.
Cyborg Franky, with a bounty
of 44 million berries.
This is awful.
Big bro's wanted by the world government.
What are we going to do now?
Yeah, that's the question.
I was happy when I found
out we didn't have bounties.
But then this had to happen.
Everyone in the whole
city knows about our bro.
He can't stay in Water 7 anymore.
And if he gets arrested again,
I don't think we'll have the power
to save him like we did last time.
But I'm sure he worried about us, too.
knowing him he probably wouldn't
leave the island no matter how much
we begged him that's why we came to
you we have no other choice we're
begging you here Straw Hats even if
he tries to fight you gotta take our
bro out to sea with you come on his
parents were pirates it's in his blood